thinking about what seems to be calling
to my thinking anyways or what my
thinking seems to be responding to the
sense of anonymity and I really think
what it's what the thought is is this
sense of that what's worthy of being
present to of a tuning to is that which
is hidden but also in this way that's
not a it isn't a unhiding it it's not a
it's not a like an unveiling
it's a revealing so you could say what
is the task in being able to become
present to that which is hidden
or another way of saying that is that
which is withdrawing yet lingering
something or doing something adds it
withdrawals that sense make that that
sense which I think modern modern
thinking or postmodern say King would
call it and rightly so it would call it
highly unusable so I guess what I've set
what I'm actually I think what I'm
actually referring to here is to be able
to think what what is it useful what
can't be used however
is deeply determinant and the way
beating is today and to look for being
right to become present to what is seems
you require the the revelation of how
much it is in fact withdrawn in such a
way in such a deep way yet there's an
intimacy when you see this withdrawing
and I think that's why it's it I keep
circling around this the sense of
anonymity right the in a certain way
being the being of beings as Heidegger
would say
his present as anonymous
I mean like what's what what is meant by
that so what is it two people present as
anonymous or it's actually I think what
it is it's not present as anonymous it's
the way being his presence is anonymous
because what isn't being said is that
there's something called being that then
presents itself anonymously and it kind
of implies that well if if we get peek
at it then we would know who being is
right but it's because we don't know
what being is that it's anonymous I
think what I think what's being thought
here is know the anonymity
is what is being sent
so what is it to tune into and be
attuned by this deep sense of a nativity
I think there's a hint to this one of
the hints is in the movie American
Beauty
there's a scene
have like a culminating scene where the
boy who it's basically that you know the
whole movie said it's incentive you know
sat in suburban help essentially and
everything that comes with post
modernity and yet the boy who goes
around filming everything who kind of
shows up on one level like a weirdo to
everybody but in actuality he is somehow
listening to something that no one else
can really see or hear and it culminates
in this moment where him and his
girlfriend who is somebody that's
beginning to hear what he hears he's
showing her one of these videos and it
it basically is a video of a of a piece
of trash of a plastic bag being blown
around and with these leaves and it's
you could watch it it's doing this dance
and he said something really interesting
is like this was he said something like
to the effect of it was this moment that
I realized
a deeply benevolent force behind things
and I this sense of and you really get a
sense of that movie in that movie in
that scene in the mood of the scene a
way in which that anonymity of being
reveals itself
within and behind the most unlooked at
unnoticed uninteresting thing leaves
wind in a piece of trash yet he was able
to listen and hear it so I think the
really the question is right is maybe
not how is it that I you we find the
Senate if ax t but rather like how is it
that one becomes available to be
addressed by that which is hidden behind
things